[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which American soft drink company was established by pharmacist Claude A. Hatcher in 1905?", "correct_answer": "Royal Crown Cola Corp.", "incorrect_answers": ["Tropical Fantasy", "National Beverage Corp.", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what way should an animal be slaughtered in order to be suitable for eating according to Jewish dietary laws?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["In a single cutting movement", "With a sharp unserrated knife", "By a trained person"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which U.S. writer of detective fiction worked for the famous Pinkerton National Detective Agency?", "correct_answer": "Dashiell Hammett", "incorrect_answers": ["Mickey Spillane", "Mary Higgins Clark", "Louis LAmour"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many muscles are in the human body?", "correct_answer": "640", "incorrect_answers": ["1000", "150", "320"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The larger the penguin species, the colder the region in which it is found.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the location of the oldest mall in England.", "correct_answer": "Oxford", "incorrect_answers": ["Canterbury", "Surrey", "Kent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the first of the murderers of Eric and Shelly to be killed by the Crow in the self-titled movie?", "correct_answer": "Tin Tin", "incorrect_answers": ["Fun Boy", "T-Bird", "Skank"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor plays a 121 years old character who tells a news reporter about his life with the Indians and the battle of Little Big Horn?", "correct_answer": "Dustin Hoffman", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Duvall", "Gene Hackman", "Sir Laurence Olivier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of food is the traditional South African meal Sosatie?", "correct_answer": "Skewered meat", "incorrect_answers": ["Seafood soup", "Cheese", "Meatballs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What statement is true about Jack Nicholsons character, Melvin Udall, in the 1997comedy movie As Good as It Gets?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["He is an Anti-Semite", "He is a racist", "He is a homophobe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actress and singer was initially offered to direct and play the role of Ingrid in the 2002 movie White Oleander, but she turned it down.", "correct_answer": "Barbra Streisand", "incorrect_answers": ["Vanessa Williams", "Cher", "Whitney Houston"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word refers to a specialized type of building in a garden that is used for the growing of citrus trees?", "correct_answer": "Orangery", "incorrect_answers": ["Orange garden", "Orangeton", "Orange-greenhouse"]}]